{
    "questions" : [
        {
            "Question" : "Q. What should I do to sing higher notes,,?",
            "Answer" : "A. Sleep well",
            "Reference" : "Imawa Imade Chikaiwa Emide : Limited Edition booklet"
        },
        {
            "Question" : "Q. When I recommend ZTMY the response I get is 'what kind of singer are they?' (It sound's like a song's name)",
            "Answer" : "A. Sorry...",
            "Reference" : "Imawa Imade Chikaiwa Emide : Limited Edition booklet"
        },
        {
            "Question" : "Q. When I call a portable charger (lit. mobile battery) a storage battery (lit. chikuden) people don't understand me ",
            "Answer" : "A. You're cool",
            "Reference" : "Imawa Imade Chikaiwa Emide : Limited Edition booklet"
        },
        {
            "Question" : "Q. It's such a shame that there aren't that many people around me who know about ZTMY that in reverse I wonder why they've not heard of you",
            "Answer" : "A. Sorry... ",
            "Reference" : "Imawa Imade Chikaiwa Emide : Limited Edition booklet"
        },
        {
            "Question" : "Q. What's your favourite style of hotpot dish, ACANE? ",
            "Answer" : "A. Chinese style.",
            "Reference" : "Imawa Imade Chikaiwa Emide : Limited Edition booklet"
        },
        {
            "Question" : "Q. Do you like Daft Punk? You used them in one of your stories didn't you?? I love ZTMY,,",
            "Answer" : "A. LOVE Technologic LOVE ",
            "Reference" : "Imawa Imade Chikaiwa Emide : Limited Edition booklet"
        },
        {
            "Question" : "Q. Do you like cooking, ACANE?",
            "Answer" : "A. I do. I want a pressure cooker",
            "Reference" : "Imawa Imade Chikaiwa Emide : Limited Edition booklet"
        },
        {
            "Question" : "Q. Tell us about some things that have made you go 'ahh, life is so peaceful right now...' recently",
            "Answer" : "A1. When I see people perform habits that they always do.\nA2. My heart is at peace when the rubbish bin is large.",
            "Reference" : "Imawa Imade Chikaiwa Emide : Limited Edition booklet"
        },
        {
            "Question" : "Q. Please give Zutomayo fans a fanname",
            "Answer" : "A. Zutomaro",
            "Reference" : "Imawa Imade Chikaiwa Emide : Limited Edition booklet"
        },
        {
            "Question" : "Q. I really wanted to talk to you ACANE so I thought of lots to say but nothing is coming to mind now! I'll continue suppo-",
            "Answer" : "A. Thank youu",
            "Reference" : "Imawa Imade Chikaiwa Emide : Limited Edition booklet"
        },
        {
            "Question" : "Q. Nice to meet you! I'm always listening to your songs. What's a type of ice cream that you like?",
            "Answer" : "A. Yogurt",
            "Reference" : "Imawa Imade Chikaiwa Emide : Limited Edition booklet"
        },
        {
            "Question" : "Q. Is ZTMY female?",
            "Answer" : "A. Probably",
            "Reference" : "Imawa Imade Chikaiwa Emide : Limited Edition booklet"
        },
        {
            "Question" : "Q. I love the smell that comes from a macdonalds paper bag",
            "Answer" : "A. I feel you",
            "Reference" : "Imawa Imade Chikaiwa Emide : Limited Edition booklet"
        },
        {
            "Question" : "Q. Do you like bricks?",
            "Answer" : "A. I've heard an engineer say 'I love bricks' before.",
            "Reference" : "Imawa Imade Chikaiwa Emide : Limited Edition booklet"
        },
        {
            "Question" : "Q. Your breakfast today?",
            "Answer" : "A. A hotdog dressed with curry stir fried cabbage",
            "Reference" : "Imawa Imade Chikaiwa Emide : Limited Edition booklet"
        },
        {
            "Question" : "Q. It takes me a day's worth of energy to decipher ZTMY's lyrics.",
            "Answer" : "A. Sorry..",
            "Reference" : "Imawa Imade Chikaiwa Emide : Limited Edition booklet"
        },
        {
            "Question" : "Q. ACAne's favortie nabe",
            "Answer" : "1st - Chinese-style hotpot\n2nd - Kimchi hotpot\n3rd - Shabu shabu\n4nd - Pot-au-feu",
            "Reference" : "Imawa Imade Chikaiwa Emide : Limited Edition booklet"
        },
        {
            "Question" : "Q. ACANE, why is ‘Ne’ (this character -> ね) the only part of your name written with a Japanese hiragana character?",
            "Answer" : "A. Because it’s my favourite Japanese hiragana character.",
            "Reference" : "Imawa Imade Chikaiwa Emide : Limited Edition booklet"
        },
        {
            "Question" : "Q. Other than the fire goby do you have any favourite fish?",
            "Answer" : "A. Mackerel",
            "Reference" : "Imawa Imade Chikaiwa Emide : Limited Edition booklet"
        },
        {
            "Question" : "Q. Are there any plans to make Uniguri-kun goods?",
            "Answer" : "A. There are. They’re still just a lump of ideas so we can’t do anything yet.",
            "Reference" : "Imawa Imade Chikaiwa Emide : Limited Edition booklet"
        },
        {
            "Question" : "Q. All the pro commentators on television look like they’re best friends with each other... It’s just one of those things",
            "Answer" : "A. Ho-",
            "Reference" : "Imawa Imade Chikaiwa Emide : Limited Edition booklet"
        },
        {
            "Question" : "Q. I like the smell of paper bags",
            "Answer" : "A. I feel you",
            "Reference" : "Imawa Imade Chikaiwa Emide : Limited Edition booklet"
        },
        {
            "Question" : "Q. I wonder why kombu doesn’t create soup stock while it’s in the sea",
            "Answer" : "A. In the first place do kombu continuously breathe soup stock while in the sea?",
            "Reference" : "Imawa Imade Chikaiwa Emide : Limited Edition booklet"
        },
        {
            "Question" : "Q. Water tastes nice so I wonder why they don’t sell water flavoured ice cream.",
            "Answer" : "A. Water flavoured sounds good yeah. Water",
            "Reference" : "Imawa Imade Chikaiwa Emide : Limited Edition booklet"
        },
        {
            "Question" : "Q. Do you look up when you're thinking?",
            "Answer" : "A. I look far",
            "Reference" : "Imawa Imade Chikaiwa Emide : Limited Edition booklet"
        },
        {
            "Question" : "Q. Me: 'You like ZTMY!? Isn't Saturn such a great song!' Friend: 'Nah the only song I know is Byoushin wo Kamu anyway'",
            "Answer" : "A. Sorry..",
            "Reference" : "Imawa Imade Chikaiwa Emide : Limited Edition booklet"
        },
        {
            "Question" : "Q. I think chocolate coronets taste the best but no one agrees with me. Everyone thinks melon bread.",
            "Answer" : "A. I like bacon prawn bread",
            "Reference" : "Imawa Imade Chikaiwa Emide : Limited Edition booklet"
        },
        {
            "Question" : "Q. International fans love u♡ur music has helped us through hard times we all thank u ♡",
            "Answer" : "A. Thank u…",
            "Reference" : "Imawa Imade Chikaiwa Emide : Limited Edition booklet"
        },
        {
            "Question" : "Q. What kinds of smells do you like?",
            "Answer" : "A. Soap",
            "Reference" : "Imawa Imade Chikaiwa Emide : Limited Edition booklet"
        },
        {
            "Question" : "Q. Is there anything you pay particular attention to regarding your voice? I'll be supporting you!",
            "Answer" : "A. Getting sleep. Thank you",
            "Reference" : "Imawa Imade Chikaiwa Emide : Limited Edition booklet"
        },
        {
            "Question" : "Q. Do you eat stew with rice?",
            "Answer" : "A. I'm in the 'stew by itself' group",
            "Reference" : "Imawa Imade Chikaiwa Emide : Limited Edition booklet"
        },
        {
            "Question" : "Q. Monkeys are scary",
            "Answer" : "A. Disco balls are scary (tl note: refence to MIRABO lyrics)",
            "Reference" : "Imawa Imade Chikaiwa Emide : Limited Edition booklet"
        },
        {
            "Question" : "Q. ...so I like ZUTOMAYO",
            "Answer" : "A. Thank you..",
            "Reference" : "Imawa Imade Chikaiwa Emide : Limited Edition booklet"
        },
        {
            "Question" : "Q. Do you have any pets?",
            "Answer" : "A. I'm allergic to animals so..",
            "Reference" : "Imawa Imade Chikaiwa Emide : Limited Edition booklet"
        },
        {
            "Question" : "Q. Do you have monolid or two eyelids or three eyelids?",
            "Answer" : "A. 2.5 eyelids",
            "Reference" : "Imawa Imade Chikaiwa Emide : Limited Edition booklet"
        },
        {
            "Question" : "What?",
            "Answer" : "What?",
            "Reference" : "Imawa Imade Chikaiwa Emide : Limited Edition booklet"
        },
        {
            "Question" : "Q : What guitar do you have?",
            "Answer" : "A : I have a Yamaha LL16 acoustic guitar. (The current guitar she plays in her Twitter videos)",
            "Reference" : "ACAne Peing Q&A"
        },
        {
            "Question" : "Q: Why do you use the letter C in Acane instead of K? (The romanji for her name,茜, is Akane)",
            "Answer" : "A : The letter C has a rounder sound than K.",
            "Reference" : "ACAne Peing Q&A"
        },
        {
            "Question" : "Q : Do you have any tips for playing guitar?",
            "Answer" : "A : tips... I want to know either, I want to mute well where it needs to be.",
            "Reference" : "ACAne Peing Q&A"
        },
        {
            "Question" : "Q : What was the first CD you bought?",
            "Answer" : "A : I think it was Kaede Kimura’s album scratch.",
            "Reference" : "ACAne Peing Q&A"
        },
        {
            "Question" : "Q : When did you start to play the guitar?",
            "Answer" : "A : Around second year of High School.",
            "Reference" : "ACAne Peing Q&A"
        },
        {
            "Question" : "Q : Planning to do a live outside of Tokyo?",
            "Answer" : "A : Not for now, but I’m thinking about Shikoku.",
            "Reference" : "ACAne Peing Q&A"
        },
        {
            "Question" : "Q : How can I get the courage to act?",
            "Answer" : "A : I always feel that before regretting no acting, I should at least try first.\nMaybe because of my lack of courage.",
            "Reference" : "ACAne Peing Q&A"
        },
        {
            "Question" : "Q : What kind of job do you think you would do if you weren’t a musician?",
            "Answer" : "A : Dietician.",
            "Reference" : "ACAne Peing Q&A"
        },
        {
            "Question" : "Q : Do you have any new year goals?",
            "Answer" : "A : Play the electric guitar live\nTry to post videos where I sing\nOriginal song on Youtube\n10,000 followers\nRelease a CD\nThese are my goals so far.",
            "Reference" : "ACAne Peing Q&A"
        },
        {
            "Question" : "Q : Are there any other instruments you would like to play besides the guitar?",
            "Answer" : "A : Banjo!",
            "Reference" : "ACAne Peing Q&A"
        },
        {
            "Question" : "Q : Please tell us what made you decide to play the guitar! Also, what made you decide to become a singer?",
            "Answer" : "A : Actually I wanted to be in a band, and I was told 'you could’ve done it someday!'\nSo I began writing songs and it was very fun.(roughly..) The decisive fact was my groundless confidence! (roughly..)",
            "Reference" : "ACAne Peing Q&A"
        },
        {
            "Question" : "Q : What made you happy the most this year?",
            "Answer" : "A : I was complimented for my original song! Also, I was able to make a really",
            "Reference" : "ACAne Peing Q&A"
        }        
    ]
}